In this exercise, you're asked to compute what an RTO might be for a given situation.
在此练习中 将要求您计算 RTO 可能针对给定情境的内容
Let's take a look. At time zero, the problem occurs.
我们来看看 在时间为零的情况下 发生问题
If it takes five minutes for an amount of time to pass before an alert is triggered,
如果在触发警报之前需要五分钟时间才能传递警报
another minute to actually trigger on call staff,
还有一分钟就会触发呼叫人员
10 minutes to get staff out of bed to get their computers to log on.
10 分把员工从床上取出来让他们的电脑登录
Another 10 minutes before they can really start diagnosing the issue,
还有 10 分的时间他们才能真正开始诊断这个问题
15 minutes to discover the root cause,
15 分发现根本原因
five more minutes to begin remediation,
再进行五分钟的修复
and another 10 minutes to actually have that remediation completed,
还有 10 分的修复完成
looking at a total time of 56 minutes.
总时间为 56 分
In this case, an RTO of one hour for this incident would be reasonable.
在此情况下 此事件的一个小时的 RTO 是合理的